1995年初 一名徒步旅行者在俄勒冈州中部偏远山区失踪
在几次目击之后 一些与世隔绝的当地社区成员开始猜测
失踪男子感染了一种他们称之为"山热"的动物传播病毒
之前在这里生活的土著人称它为
玛伊冈·奥登瓦恩 或者"狼面人"
起床了
Ten-hut!
带上你的装备 我们七点出发
Grab your hunting pack. We're leaving at 0700.
这景色永不过时 对吧
This view never gets old, does it?
百看不厌
No matter how many times you see it.
啊 别靠近这些东西
Ah, don't go anywhere near those.
这些叫死亡帽蘑菇 这名字可不是开玩笑的
These are death cap mushrooms. The name ain't kidding.
吃一个 你马上就进太平间
Eat one of those, you'll be wearing a toe tag real quick
除非有人为你准备了一个全新的肝脏
unless someone's got a brand-new liver
马上给你换上
lying around for you.
布莱克 布莱克
Blake. Blake.
布莱克
Blake.
你听到我说的了吗
Did you hear what I just said?
听到了
Yes, sir.
我说了什么
What did I say?
别吃这些蘑菇
Don't eat the mushrooms.
这些蘑菇叫什么
What are they called?
嗯…
Uh...
看吧 我就说你没听我讲话
See, this is what I'm talking about-- you're not hearing me.
你还活在你自己该死的世界里
You're off in your own goddamn world somewhere.
这个地方很美 但也很危险
This place is beautiful. It's also dangerous.
如果你知道该怎么做 你就能生存下去
You can survive if you know exactly what to do.
是
Yes, sir.
大家就是这样被夺走了…
People get taken from you-- like that.
死并不难
It's not hard to die.
这是世界上最简单的事
It's the easiest thing in the world.
我们都
We are all...
与它咫尺之遥
inches away from it.
我没办法一直在你身边保护你
And I'm not always gonna be around to watch over you,
但我会确保你清楚
but I'm gonna make damn sure that you know
如何生存下去 因为
how to survive as...
布莱克
Blake.
你知道你需要待在我身边的
You know you need to stay near me.
他妈的就待在我身边 小子
Right fucking next to me, boy!
如果你不按我说的做 你会受伤的
If you don't do what I say, you get hurt.
你想受伤吗 想吗
Do you want to get hurt?! Huh?
你想受伤吗
Do you want to get hurt?!
不 我不想 只是
No, sir, I don't. I just...
我只是想更容易打到鹿而已
I wanted to get a better shot at the deer.
到打鹿台去
Get up in that deer blind.
赶快
Now.
捂住耳朵
Cover your ears.
怎么了 爸爸
What was it, Dad?
就一头熊
A bear.
山谷这边到处都是
They're all over this side of the valley.
稍作调整 我们走
Pick yourself up, and let's go
趁着天还有点光亮
while there's still some light left.
基尔714 这里是洛威尔819
Kiel 714, this is Lovell 819.
基尔714 这里是洛威尔819 能听到吗
Kiel 714, this is Lovell 819. Do you read me?
你到底在哪儿 丹
Where in the hell are you, Dan?
怎么了 格雷迪
DAN : What is it, Grady?
丹
Dan.
我看到了
I saw it.
看到什么了
DAN: Saw what?
你知道我说的是什么
You know what I'm talking about.
那个徒步旅行的人吗
DAN: That hiker?
狼面人吗
The face of the wolf?
丹 那是真的
Dan, it's real.
我在瞄准镜了看到它了
I had it in my scope.
我差点就打中了
I almost shot it.
格雷迪 天黑以后
DAN: Grady, what is the point
还上山找不并想
in going up that mountain after dark
被发现的东西有什么意义吗
looking for something that doesn't want to be found?
我不是在找它
I wasn't looking for it.
我当时正在河边猎鹿
I was hunting deer down by the river.
它在我儿子后面出现了
And it came after my boy.
我会抓到它的 丹
I'm gonna get it, Dan.
你得跟我一起去
And you got to come with me.
难道你不想保证你儿子的安全吗
Don't you want to keep your boy safe?
我们能吃冰淇淋吗
Can we get some ice cream?
可以吗 求你了 求你了 求你了
Please? Please, please, please, please, please, please...
我在博物馆给你买过热巧克力了
I got you a hot chocolate at the museum.
那都不是甜点啊
That's not a dessert.
那是饮料
That's a drink.
哦 我觉得那算是甜点 大小姐
Oh, I think it's dessert, missy.
你知道你是全世界最好的爸爸吗
Well, did you know you're the best dad in the whole world?
知道啊 可是我敢肯定
Yeah, I'm sure the timing of that
这个跟冰淇淋没关系
has nothing to do with the ice cream.
是没有啊 我就是想告诉你
It doesn't. I just wanted to tell you.
我很认真的
I'm serious.
哎 怎么感觉像是场交易啊
Eh, this feels very transactional.
我可不懂这是什么意思
I don't know what that means.
嘿 下来
Hey, get down.
宝贝儿
Ginger.
马上给我下来
Get down right now.
好吧 你这样 就没冰淇淋吃了
Okay, that's it, no ice cream
3 2 1
in three, two, one.
狗他妈的就不会乱跑乱撞
No, the dog don't jump off the motherfucking leash!
嘿 嘿 嘿
Hey, hey, hey.
我跟你说了下来
I told you to get down.
为什么就不听我的话啊见鬼
Why didn't you listen to me, damn it?
为什么不听话
Why didn't you listen to me?
对不起
I'm sorry.
对不起 我发脾气了
I'm sorry I lost my temper.
刚才那不是我
That's not me.
我不想这样子
I don't want to be like that.
我只是需要你在我跟你讲事情的时候好好听着
I just need you to listen when I tell you something.
因为我的什么职责呢
'Cause what's my job?
保证你女儿的安全
To keep your daughter safe.
对 是这样
Yeah. That's right.
那你的职责呢
And what's your job?
读心术
To read minds.
你能读出我现在在想什么吗
Can you guess what I'm thinking right now?
"我爱我的小女儿"
"I love my little girl."
太厉害了吧
That's amazing.
我就是这么想的
That's exactly what I was thinking.
你是怎么做到的
How do you do that every time?
你可太擅长了
You're so good at your job.
好了
Okay.
很抱歉 你吓到我了 好吗
I'm sorry. You scared me, okay?
-你欠我一美元 -为什么啊
-You owe me a dollar. -Why?
因为你爆粗口了
Because you sweared.
我没有 你幻听了
No, I didn't. You're hearing things.
没幻听 爸爸 你就是爆粗口了
I'm not, Daddy. You sweared.
好了 我给你涂上吧
Okay, now let me put some on you.
哦 天呐 好吧 搞快点
Oh, my God. Okay, do it quickly.
-真好看 -嗯哼 好看吗
-Beautiful. -Mm-hmm. Good?
-好看啊 -怎么样
-Yeah. -How's this?
你看起来好恐怖啊
You look creepy.
你是说这样吗
You mean like this?
-你是说这样吗 宝贝儿 -爸爸
-You mean like this, Ginger? -Dad.
不 额 好吧 不 我明白了
No, uh, yeah. No, I get that.
好啦 坐到桌边去吧
Okay, go sit at the table.
不 可是 我 我有第二个消息源的
No, but I-I have, I have a second source.
等一下
One minute.
那你是要把它报道出去
Well, are you gonna ship it
还是要让《泰晤士报》再挖我们的墙角呢
or you gonna let the Times scoop us again?
- 嗨 -嗨 妈咪
-Hi. -Hi, Mommy.
那我们就这么说定了
Well, so we have a deal then?
什么鬼 胡说八道
What-- This is bullshit.
你以前从未要求过这个
You've never asked for this before.
额 有处理这些破问题的时间
Uh, in the time it takes to do all of this,
我们本可以走在所有人前面的
we could've gotten ahead of everybody.
我觉得我们没必要管那么多了
But I just don't think we need to do it.
我保证可以现在就开始 你能上网吗
I promise from now on. Can you just get it online?
-去别的房间吧 -嘘
-Take that in the other room. -Shh.
我本不该这么做的
I shouldn't be doing this.
你做还是不做
Are you doing it or not?
夏洛特 你能去别的房间接吗
Charlotte, can you take that in the other room?
听着 我 我知道自己在做什么
Listen, I-I know what I'm doing.
你清楚我是知道的 因为就是你教的我
You know I know because you taught me how to do it.
再见 夏洛特
Goodbye, Charlotte.
好吧 再见
Okay. Bye.
你能 额
Can you, um...
你能不能不要这样
Can you not do that, please?
我怎么了
What did I do?
我刚才在跟我的编辑进行一次重要的谈话
I was having an important conversation with my editor.
对 因为只有你
Yeah, 'cause you're the only one
有重要的事情要做 是吧
that has important stuff going on, right?
我都完全没事做的
I'm not busy at all.
如果我有孩子 我绝不会在他们面前吵架
If I ever have kids, I'm never gonna fight in front of them.
我们没有吵架 亲爱的
We're not fighting, honey.
我们正在进行热烈的交流
We're having a spirited exchange.
好吧
Okay.
所以 额
So, um...
我刚刚得知我爸最终还是被宣布去世了
I just found out my dad has been finally declared deceased.
俄勒冈州的官方说法
Officially, by the state of Oregon.
额 抱歉了
Um, I'm sorry.
没事
It's okay.
你感觉怎么样
How do you feel?
我是说 我们知道这封信总有一天会寄出的
I mean, we knew this letter was coming one day.
可是最后
But the finality of it...
是啊 我不知道 我还有些懵
Yeah, I don't know, it's still shocking.
是啊
Yeah.
你很难过吗 爸爸
Are you sad, Daddy?
我是难过的
I am, yeah.
我为很多事情感到难过
I'm sad about a lot of things.
真希望我能更了解他一些
I wish I'd known him better.
可他总是会让我害怕
But he always made me afraid of him,
所以我一长大就离开了
so as soon as I was old enough, I left.
我们很久没有聊过了
We hadn't spoken in a long time
因为我选择不说
because I chose not to.
额 而现在我再也不能和他讲话了
Um, and now that I can't speak to him...
我突然很想跟他聊聊
...I suddenly want to.
一整天
The whole day.
不可能 整件事都很荒唐啊
No way. The whole thing felt ridiculous, you know?
哦
Oh.
我待会儿去找你们
I'll catch up with you guys later.
好
Yeah.
嘿
Hey.
惊喜啊
This is a surprise.
我给你带了午饭
I brought you some lunch.
谢谢
Thank you.
我们很久没有这个样子了
We haven't done this in a while.
是啊
Yeah.
你开心吗 夏洛特
Are you happy, Charlotte?
开心啊
Yeah.
是啊
那你呢
Are-are you?
为 为什么要这么问
Why-why are you asking me that?
因为我觉得我们做的并不好
Because I don't think we're doing well right now.
我来这里是因为
I came here because
当我收到那封信的时候
when I got that letter...
我突然意识到
...it dawned on me
你跟宝贝儿是我唯一的亲人了
that you and Ginger are the only family that I have left.
我们与人相处的时间是如此短暂
We have such a short amount of time with people.
我只希望我们都还在的时候
I just want us to enjoy each other
能取悦彼此 努力让家庭幸福
and try to be happy as a family while we are here.
我也想开心 可是
I want to be happy, too, but...
我在想 你应该跟我一起去俄勒冈
I was thinking you should come up to Oregon with me.
我得去一趟
I have to go up there
把我爸的东西都打包装车
and pack up all my dad's stuff in a truck.
咱们为什么不一起去呢
Why don't we all go together?
我们可以在那儿一起过整个夏天
We'd spend the whole summer up there.
我感觉对我们是件好事
I think it'd be good for us.
那个地方相当让人惊叹
It really is stunning.
离农场不远有个山谷
There's this valley not far from the farm.
就在这两座山之间
It's between these mountains.
无论你看多少次 那景色都会
And no matter how many times you see it,
让你觉得一切会好起来的
the view makes you feel like everything's gonna be okay.
我想让你跟宝贝儿去看看
I want you and Ginger to see it.
听起来不错啊 可我工作走不开啊
It sounds nice, but I can't just leave work.
是 不过你可以远程工作啊
No, yeah, but you can work remotely.
休息一段时间吧
Just take some time off.
宝贝儿会很开心的
Ginger would love that.
你可以花点时间陪陪她
You could spend some time with her.
你也能写你的书了
You can work on your book.
是啊 我不
Yeah, I don't...
我甚至都不知道自己还擅不擅长了
I don't even know if I'm good at that anymore.
你是个好作家呀
You're a great writer. Come on.
我是说陪女儿
I meant at spending time with my daughter.
她
She...
相比于我 她跟你更亲近
She relates to you so much more than me.
你是一位了不起的母亲
You are an incredible mother.
你是的 馁
You are.
跟我去吧
Come with me.
好了 好了 我想到一个
Okay, okay, I've got one.
嗯 你是住在水里吗
Mm, do you live in water?
不是
Nope.
好吧
Okay.
你住在森林里吗
Do you live in the forest?
有时候吧
Sometimes.
嗯 你会飞吗
Mm, can you fly?
不会
Nope.
你是用四条腿走路吗
Do you walk on four legs?
-是啊 -是吗
-Yes. -Yeah?
哦 你是头鹿吗
Oh, are you a deer?
额 不是
Uh... no.
额 那你是头熊吗
Uh, are you a bear?
不是
No.
是狗吗
Are you a dog?
不是
No.
不 我只是不知道
No. I just don't know what...
不知道答案
Don't know the answer.
-不 我是头麑 -麑吗
-No, I'm a fawn. -A fawn?
-对 -我说过鹿了呀
-Yeah. -I said deer.
-麑不是鹿 -是
-A fawn is not a deer. -It's-it's...
-不是的 -什么啊 就是鹿的小时候啊
-It's not. -What? It's literally a baby deer.
不是的
It's not.
魔生活在森林里 好不好
And fawns live in the forest. Hello.
它们有时在森林里 但有时
They do sometimes, but sometimes
它们会出现在人们的后院 所以
they're in people's backyards, so...
-哦 哦 -什么 那是
-Oh. Oh. -What? That's...
哦 你骗人 你知道吗
Oh, you are a cheater. You know what?
-这样吧 你知道我要干什么吗 -别 爸爸 住手
-That's it. You know what's coming? -Don't, Daddy. Stop.
-爸爸 停下来 不要啊 妈咪 -喔呼 喔呼
-Daddy, stop. No, Mommy. -Uh-oh. Uh-oh.
-跟爸爸说让他成熟点啊 -喔呼
-Tell Daddy he's being immature. -Uh-oh.
嘿 嘿 我是可以跟他一样不成熟哟
Hey, hey, I can be just as immature as he can.
妈咪 不要啊 停下来啊 妈咪
Mommy, stop it. Stop, Mommy.
你凭什么觉得我很成熟啊
What makes you think I'm so mature?
-啊 啊 -不要啊 妈咪 停下来
-Huh? Huh? -Stop it, Mommy. Stop.
求你了妈咪 别闹啦
Please, Mommy, stop it.
-妈咪 不要啦 -求我
-Mommy, stop it. -Please?
求你啦 妈咪 别闹啦
Please, Mommy, stop.
等等 这就是吗 该死
Wait, is this it? Shit.
-爸爸 -抱歉 亲爱的 我的错
-Dad. -Sorry, honey. Shivers.
我看下地图
Let me check the map here.
我手机没有信号
I have no service.
我也是
Me, either.
不过这里看起来确实很眼熟
This does look familiar, though.
我可以看看吗
Can I see?
树屋里有人
There's someone in that tree house.
哪里
Where?
那边
Over there.
她说得对 那东西里面有人
She's right-- there's someone inside that thing.
哦
Oh.
额 我们走吧 布莱克
Uh, let's go, Blake.
不 没关系的
No, it's okay.
不行啊 他有枪
No, he has a gun.
夏洛特 这里每个人都有枪的
Charlotte, everyone around here has a gun.
布莱克 咱能开车走人吗
Blake, can-can you just please drive?
-晚上好 -嘿
-MAN: Evening. -Hey.
你们要去哪儿啊
Where you guys headed?
额 我在找我爸的农场
Uh, I'm looking for my dad's farm.
我只是有段时间没来了 忘记怎么走
I just, I haven't been up here in a while. I forgot...
你爸是谁
Who's your dad?
额 格雷迪
Uh... Grady.
洛威尔
Lovell.
你可是离开很久了 布雷克
You've been gone a long time, Blake.
等等 我 我认识你吗
Wait, do I... do I know you?
我是德里克 我是丹·基尔的儿子
I'm Derek. I'm Dan Kiel's son.
是哦
Right.
哦 德里克 见鬼
Oh, Derek. Shit.
-爸爸 -哦 不好意思
-Dad. -Oh, sorry.
是啊 我记得你
Yeah, no, I remember you.
你好吗 很高兴见到你
How are you? It's good to see you.
住在这里的人已经不多了
Not many of us left living up here anymore.
都不算是整个世界的一部分了
Not really a part of the world.
是啊 我再同意不过了
Yeah. I-I'd agree with that.
你可能不记得了 但是 额一般来说
You might not remember this, but, uh, for the most part,
我们不喜欢天黑后上山的
we don't like to be out after dark on the mountain.
这里没有电 没有灯
There's no power grid, no lights.
哦 我还以为只是我爸这样
Oh. I-I thought that was just my dad.
额 你知道 我其实有点迷路了
Uh, you know, I'm actually a little lost.
我确定这是他的车道
You know, I-I was sure that this was his driveway.
不是的
It's not.
真的吗
Really?
这是我的
It's mine.
哦
Oh.
好吧
Yeah, okay.
抱歉了
Well, sorry.
通往格雷迪家的那条老路被切断了
The usual road to Grady's is cut off.
我带你过去吧 让你快点安顿下来
I'll take you there, get you settled in quicker.
好的
Okay.
布莱克 不 绝对不行
Blake, no. No, absolutely not.
-没关系的 让他给咱带路 -不 他
-It's fine. Let him show us. -No, he...
为什么他不能告诉我们怎么走呢
Why can't he just tell us where it is?
-他现在就在这儿了 -什么 那
-He's standing there now. -What, so...
-开门吧 小夏 -你在说什么
-Just open the door, Char. -What are you talk...
-他已经在开了 -别
-He's opening it. -Well, stop...
嗨 嗨
Hi. Hi.
嗨 额 不 不 不
Hi. Uh, no, no, no.
没关系 我坐到后面去吧
It's okay. I-I'll just go to the back.
谢谢 女士
Thank you, ma'am.
看好脚
Watch your feet.
往前走一段路就到了
Just go straight on a ways.
嘿 小可爱
Hey there, cutie.
额 德雷克 这是我女儿和我妻子夏洛特
Uh, Derek, that's Ginger and my wife Charlotte.
嗨
Hi.
你们打算待多久
How long you planning on staying?
-待不长 -就一阵子
-Not too long. -A little while.
这绝对是一种后天养成的味道
It's definitely an acquired taste.
在这里 有些事你不得不去接受
There are things you have to come to terms with up here.
动物
Animals.
疾病
Diseases.
我们都是很坚强的人
Well, we're, we're pretty tough people.
是这样吗
Is that so?
在我看来 你们并不坚强
To me, you don't seem so tough.
这是件好事情
That's a good thing.
说明你们过得不错
Means you got a good life.
你们健康 安全
You're healthy, safe.
你爸的家就在前面
Your dad's place is just up ahead.
你是做什么工作的 布雷克
What do you do for a living, Blake?
我是个作家
I'm a writer.
不过现在正处于工作间隙
I'm between jobs right now, though.
所以 我是后面
So... I'm a dad
那个小怪物的全职爸爸
to that monster in the back.
我是个记者
I'm a journalist.
我敢打赌 你每天看着她们都会想 你怎么会这么幸运
I bet you look at them every day and wonder how you got so lucky
拥有如此聪慧美丽的一家人
to have such a smart and beautiful family.
是的
I do.
该死
Shit.
哦
Oh.
宝贝儿 你还好吗
Ginger? Are you okay?
我没事
I'm okay.
小夏 你呢
Char, are you okay?
嘿 你伤到哪儿了吗
Hey, are you hurt anywhere?
你没事吧 宝贝儿
Are you okay? Ginger?
夏洛特 你受伤了吗
Charlotte, are you hurt?
-没有 -咦
-No. -Huh?
德雷克 你还好吗
Derek, are you okay?
嘿 嘿 不 不 不 不
Hey, hey, no, no, no, no!
哦 见鬼
Oh, shit!
好吧 我们得离开这里
Okay. We got to get out of this thing.
宝贝儿 宝贝儿
Ginger. Ginger.
-不 不 不 -宝贝儿 看着我
-No, no, no. -Ginger, look at me.
不 拜托 拜托不
No, please. Please, no.
你得从窗户爬出去
You got to climb through the window.
看着我 宝贝儿
Look at me, Ginger.
从窗户爬出去 你能做到的 亲爱的
Climb through the window. You can do it, honey.
不行 爸爸 我怕我会掉下去
No, Daddy, I'm scared I'm gonna fall.
-你不会有事的 你没事的 -我会掉下去的
-You'll be okay. You'll be okay. -I'm gonna fall.
我会掉下去的 我会掉下去的
I'm gonna fall. I'm gonna fall.
没事的 爬到上面去
It's okay. Just get onto the top.
就待在那儿
Just stay right there.
就坐那儿 亲爱的
Just sit right there, honey.
待在那儿别动 亲爱的 妈咪这就来
Just stay there, honey. Mommy's coming.
夏洛特 上
Charlotte, go.
你没事吧
You okay?
待在那儿 我这就来
Stay right there. I'm coming.
我
I...
好吧
Okay.
我们得下去 在这儿等着
We got to get down. Wait here.
来吧
Come on.
宝贝儿 亲爱的 你得跳了
Ginger, honey, you have to go.
来吧 我会接住你的
Come on. I'm gonna catch you.
好了 夏洛特 来吧
Okay. All right, Charlotte, come on.
你没事吧
Are you okay?
-没事 没事 -没事吗
-No, yeah. Yeah. Yeah. -Yeah?
宝贝儿 你受伤了吗
Ginger, are you hurt at all?
-没有 -好的 来吧
-No. -Okay, come on.
我们得走了 我们必须找到房子
We got to go. We have to find the house.
看好脚下 来 亲爱的
Watch your step. Come on, honey.
我们得加快脚步了
We got to move quick.
那里安全些 来
Where it's safer. Come on.
小心 亲爱的 小心 小心
Careful, honey. Careful, careful, careful.
-爸爸 我累了 -什么
-Daddy, I'm tired. -What?
-我走不动了 -好吧
-I can't go. -Okay.
夏洛特
Charlotte.
好的 亲爱的
Okay, honey.
快点
Quick.
来吧 我记得这里
Come on, I recognize this.
很近了
We're close.
我把你放在这儿 亲爱的 好吗
I'm gonna put you down here, honey, okay?
-好把 -手给我
-Okay. -Give me your hand.
来吧
Come on.
-来 -小心
-Come on. -Careful.
小心
Be careful.
来 来
Come on. Come on.
就是这里
This is it.
快跑
Run.
跑啊 亲爱的
Run, honey.
来啊 亲爱的
Go, honey.
快点
Come on.
快 快
Come on. Come on.
来
Come on.
爸爸 快点
Daddy, hurry up.
爸爸 快啊
Daddy, hurry up!
赶紧 进屋
Come on. Get inside.
等等 等等
Wait. Wait.
-待在这儿 -爸爸 你要去哪儿啊
-Stay right here. -Daddy, where are you going?
-我马上回来 -爸爸 爸爸
-I'll be right back. -Daddy. Daddy.
-跟妈咪待在一起 -爸爸
-Stay with Mommy. -Daddy.
好的
Okay.
该死
Shit.
爸爸
Daddy.
嗨
Hi.
嗯 没事了
Mm. It's okay.
我们安全了
We're safe.
我想回家
I want to go home.
我知道
I know.
会回去的
We will.
我们现在还不能出去 躺下吧
We just can't go outside right now. Lay down.
我们只能等到明天早上了
We just have to wait until the morning.
好吗
Okay?
不 哪儿也不要去
No, don't go anywhere.
好的 好的 我就在这儿
Okay, okay. I'm here.
我哪儿也不去
I'm not going anywhere.
我在这儿 就在这儿
I'm gonna be right here. Right here.
那个人死了吗
Is that man dead?
从树屋出来的那个人
The man who came out the tree house?
我不知道
I don't know.
大概率他死了
Most likely, he did die.
我很抱歉让你发生了这样的事
I'm so sorry that this happened to you.
保护你是我的职责
It's my job to protect you.
我却没有做到
And I didn't.
我让你经历了一件非常可怕的事情
I've put you through something very scary.
如果这件事一直这样困扰着你
And I'd never be able to forgive myself
我永远都无法原谅我自己
if this stayed with you.
你知道吗 如果这件事给你留下了伤痕
You know? If it scarred you.
你知道吗 当你是一个父亲
You know, sometimes when you're a daddy,
你会很害怕你的孩子留下伤痕的
you're so scared of your kids getting scars,
因为你就会成为给他们留下伤疤的那个人
you become the thing that scars 'em.
嘿 我现在在想什么
Hey, what am I thinking right now?
"我爱我的小女儿"
"I love my little girl."
太不可思议了
That's incredible.
你一定会读心术
You must be able to read minds,
因为我就是在想这个
because that's exactly what I was thinking.
一字不差
Word for word.
好啦
Okay.
爱你
I love you.
我就在这儿
I'll be right here.
记住 这是我的职责
Remember, that's my job.
我不会让你出任何事的
I'm not gonna let anything happen to you.
我想我们应该 额
I think we should, um...
我想我们应该把前门挡上
I think we should cover the front door,
因为如果那东西 如果它一直想进来
'cause if that thing... if it keeps trying to get in,
门上的铰链会脱落的
the whole door can come off the hinges.
刚才那是什么东西
What was it?
什么
What?
那他妈是什么鬼东西 布雷克
What the fuck was that thing, Blake?
我不知道
I don't know.
我知道听起来像动物
I know it sounded like an animal...
可当我们差点撞到它的时候 我直直地看着它
but I looked right at it when we almost hit it,
我发誓 它是用两只脚站起来的
and I swear to God it was standing up on two feet,
就像个人
like a person.
布莱克
Blake.
能撑得住吗
Is that gonna hold?
也许吧
Maybe.
我觉得我们应该试着打电话求救
I think we should try to call somebody for help.
怎么打
How?
喂 测试
Hello? Test.
喂 这里是洛威尔 819
Hello. This is Lovell 819.
有人能听到吗
Can anyone hear me?
喂
Hello?
该死
Hell...
天呐 这是什么味道
Jesus, what is that smell?
嗯 什么 你说什么
Hmm? What? What'd you say?
喂
Hello?
我找到吃的了
Well, I found something to eat.
我爸做的牛肉干
My dad's jerky.
我的下巴 一定是撞到方向盘了
My jaw. I must've hit it on the steering wheel.
哦 该死
Oh, fuck.
给你 给
Here. Here.
哦 我的天呐
Oh, my God.
好了 来坐下
Okay. Come on. Sit down.
坐好 没事的
Just sit. It's okay.
抬胳膊
Just lift your arm.
天呐
God.
我想是被卡车的窗户割伤的
I think I cut it on the window in the truck.
我不 我不知道
I-I don't... I don't know.
看起来你不像是被玻璃割伤的
This doesn't look like you got cut by glass.
好吧 好吧 额
Okay. Okay. Um...
抬起胳膊
Lift your arm up.
好了 我试一试
All right, j-just try a little bit. Just try.
谢谢
Thank you.
继续帮我试CB无线电
Keep trying the CB radio for me.
好吗
Okay?
天呐 宝贝儿
Jesus, Ginger.
对不起 我吵醒你了 亲爱的
I'm sorry I woke you, honey.
睡觉去吧 好吗 你需要休息一下
Just go back to bed, okay? You need to get your rest.
宝贝儿
Ginger.
听话 好吗
Will you listen to me, please?
回床上去 快半夜了
Go back to bed. It's almost midnight.
嘿
Hey.
你联系到CB上的什么人了吗
Did you reach anyone on the CB?
我 我没
I-I don't...
我马上就好
I'll be done in a minute.
真诡异啊
How odd.
喔
Ow.
嘘
Shh.
- 夏洛特 -布莱克 布莱克
-Charlotte. -Blake. Blake.
布莱克
Blake.
妈咪
Mommy.
-回去 回去 -妈咪 妈咪
-Get back! Get back! -Mommy. Mommy.
回去
Get back!
布莱克 布莱克
Blake. Blake.
小夏
Char?
能听到吗
Can you read me?
有谁能听到吗
Can anybody hear?
喂
Hello?
有谁能听到吗
Can anybody hear me?
这里是夏洛特·洛威尔
This is Charlotte Lovell.
如果有人能听到我的声音 请回复
If someone can hear me, please respond.
我丈夫病了
My-my husband is, uh, sick.
如果有人能听到的话
Um, if-if anyone can, uh, can hear me, uh,
请找人来帮忙
pl-please call someone to help.
我们遭到了某种动物的攻击
We were attacked by some kind of animal,
我觉得我丈夫也被感染了
and I-I think my, um, husband was infected by it.
他
He's...
他已经无法自控
He's not himself,
还有 额 他不 他不会说话了 额
and, um, he can't, he can't talk, um...
对 额 他不会说话了
Yeah, uh, he doesn't,
他好像并不知道他生病了 但是
he doesn't seem to know he's sick, but, um...
如果有人能听到 请来帮忙啊
i-if someone can hear what I'm saying, please help.
额 喂
Uh, hello?
喂
Hello?
他妈的
Goddamn it!
我好担心你
I'm so worried about you.
我不知道该怎么办
I don't know what to do.
哦 我的天呐
Oh, my God.
哦 我的天呐 快
Oh, my God. Come on.
我们上楼
Let's get you upstairs.
来吧
Come on.
给 你能 额
Here. Can you, um...
你能写下来吗
Can you write it down?
告诉我出什么事了
Just tell me what's wrong.
不
No.
你病了 仅此而已 但我们会治好你的
You're sick-- that's all-- but we're gonna fix you.
布莱克
Blake...
你会好起来的 因为咱宝贝儿需要你
You're gonna get better, because Ginger needs you.
我需要你
I need you.
没有你我办不到的
I can't do this without you.
我真正想说的是
What I-I really want to say is...
是
...is that...
我爱你 布莱克
is that I love you, Blake.
没有你 我这辈子什么也不想做了
I don't want to do anything in my life without you.
你是我最好的朋友
You're my best friend.
我太爱你了
I love you so much.
夏 夏洛特
Ch-Charlotte...
发生了什么
What is happening?
我听不明白你说话
I can't understand you.
你在说什么啊
What... what are you saying?
他怎么了
What's wrong with him?
嗨
Hi.
没事
It's okay.
过来吧
Come here.
爸爸不太舒服 等到早上
Daddy's not feeling well, but in the morning,
我们就马上带他去看医生 好吗
we're gonna take him to the doctor as soon as we can, okay?
你生病了吗 爸爸
Are you sick, Dada?
这是什么
What is this?
你怎么一直在流血
Why are you bleeding?
爸爸的胳膊为什么会这样
Why is Daddy's arm like that?
-宝贝儿 额 -帮帮他啊 妈咪
-Ginger, um... -Help him, Mommy.
宝贝儿 你去隔壁房间好吗
Baby, go to the next room, okay?
哦 我的天呐
CHARLOTTE : Oh, my God.
布莱克
Blake.
妈咪
Mommy?
好了 快点 快点
Okay, come on. Come on.
出来 出来吧 没事的
Out. Just come out. It's okay.
没事的 没事
It's okay, it's okay.
这边走 亲爱的
This way, honey.
好的 来吧 来
Okay, come on. Come on.
妈咪 要是他
Mommy, what if he...
快点 快点
Come on. Come on.
快啊
Come on.
哦 我的天呐
Oh, my God.
好的 好的
Okay, okay.
好了
Okay.
妈咪 他来了
Mommy, he's coming.
上去
Up here.
快 爬上去
Quick. Climb up here.
别动
Stay still.
妈咪
Mommy, please.
妈咪 我要掉下去了
Mommy, please, I'm gonna fall.
快
Come on.
-你丢下了他 -什么
-You left him. -What?
你把爸爸留在外面 他会受伤的
You left Daddy outside. He's gonna get hurt.
-他会死掉的 你把他丢在外面等死 -不 不
-He's gonna die! You just left him outside to die! -No. No.
不 他是在保护你
No, he was trying to protect you.
待在这儿
Stay here.
是爸爸吗
Is it Daddy?
他生病了
He's sick.
他需要我们
He needs us.
开门啊 妈咪
Open the door, Mommy.
爸爸
Daddy?
Daddy...
我现在在想什么
what am I thinking right now?
我在想什么
What am I thinking?
我在想我爱你
I was thinking that I love you.
爸爸
Daddy?
爸爸 爸爸 你能听到我说话吗
Dad? Dad, can you hear me?
爸爸 爸爸 你没事吧
Daddy? Daddy, are you okay?
我太爱你了
I love you so much.
快点 快点 起来 起来啊
Come on. Come on. Get up. Get up. Get up.
过来 过来
Come on. Come on.
爸爸
Daddy.
进来 进来
Get in. Get in.
-进来 -妈咪
-Get in. -Mommy!
妈咪
Mommy!
Mommy?
爸爸为什么会生病啊
Why did Daddy have to get sick?
呃
Um...
爸爸的父亲
Daddy's father...
不久前 他出去了 去了森林
A while ago, he went out... into the forest,
就再也没有回来
and he never came back.
所有人都以为他死了 可是
Everybody thought he was dead, but...
我想他只是病了
I think he just got sick.
跟爸爸一样的病吗
Sick like Daddy?
对
Yeah.
我想他可能
I think he may have...
把这病传染给了爸爸
given his sickness to Daddy.
我希望他回到原来的样子
I want him back the way he was.
我知道 我也是 亲爱的
I know. Me, too, honey.
我 我也希望他变回去
I-I want him back, too.
我会一直陪着你的
I'm always going to be here for you.
不 妈咪
No. Mommy.
妈咪
Mommy.
没事的
It's okay.
退后 退后 退后
Get back! Get back! Get back!
求你了 爸爸 你吓到我了
Please, Daddy, you're scaring me.
不
No.
不不
No. No.
妈咪
Mommy.
这儿 来
In here. Come.
来啊 来
Come on. Come on.
快 妈咪 他来了
Hurry, Mommy. He's coming.
给 拿着这个
Here. Just hold this.
拿好
Take it.
快点 快点
Come on. Come on.
没关系 来啊 来
All right. All right. Come on. Come on.
妈咪
Mommy.
他希望这一切都结束
He wants this to be over.
哦 布莱克
Oh, Blake.
有我在 有我在
I'm here. I'm here.
*Like a shot through the dark*
*Like an arrow to my heart*
*Somewhere in your eyes*
*There's a little smoke and flame*
*I saw you change*
*And I had to rearrange it, baby*
*Yeah*
*Remember us in cars, dirty bars and dirty hearts*
*The time it takes to burn*
*I couldn't even start to think we'd be apart*
*Or a life lived in reverse*
*'Cause somewhere back in time*
*When you and love were mine*
*-'Cause I saw you change -Change*
*And I had to rearrange it, baby*
*Yeah*
*I saw you change*
*You felt no pain*
*When you and love were mine*
*-I saw you change -Change*
*Change*
*And I had to rearrange it, baby*
*Yeah*
*I saw you change*
*-You felt no pain -Pain*
*When you and love were mine*
*And I'll see you again in red and blue*
*And I'll say it again, and I'll say it true*
*And I'll see you again*
*In red and blue.*